(Howard:)-Call him and set up an interview.
-I'm on it.
(Sheldon:)-That's happy, right?
-Yeah.
(Sheldon:)Nailed it.
(Prof Laughlin:)Dr. Koothrappali, come on in.
I was surprised to hear you're interested
in joining our team.
(Prof Laughlin:)Giving up on those
trans-Neptunian objects, are we?
(Raj:)No, no. It's a very promising area.
(Raj:)In a perfect world,
I'd spend several more years on it.
I couldn't pass up the opportunity
to work with you...
(Raj:)...on your tremendously exciting and
not yet conclusively disproved hypothesis.
Splendid. Please sit down.
(Prof Laughlin:)Can I offer you a sherry?
(Raj:)It's a little early, isn't it?
Not on Proxima Centauri. Ha, ha.
[CHUCKLING]
Oh, that's very good.
(Raj:)Jolly amusing. But if you don't mind,
I'll hold off until sunset on Titan.
Ha, ha. Well done. I have a feeling
you're going to fit in fine, Dr. Koothrappali.
(Raj:)Thank you, sir.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
(Woman:)I'm sorry. Am I late?
LAUGHLIN:
No, no. Right on time.
(Prof Laughlin:)Dr. Koothrappali,
may I present Dr. Millstone from MIT.
(Prof Laughlin:)She'll be heading up
our data analysis team.
(Dr Millstone:)It's nice to meet you, Dr. Koothrappali.